All right, let's try this. Okay, it
looks
good, but create add uh creating a new
card isn't great.
There's a uh simplistic
JavaScript
popup for the name and no way to add a
description.
This does not look professional.
not look professional.
Can it be improved?
All right, we give it its marching
orders. We'll see how it does with this.
And it's a good example of working
iteratively. And it says, "I've been
wrestling with a better UI for card
completion." Uh, Clark card creation.
So, so obviously it was already thinking
about this somewhere in the trace that
went by that I didn't read. We'll let it
do its thing and uh I'll see you back in
a second. Okay. It claims it has done
that. It says you can now click the
dashed adcard button in any column to
see the professional modal and you can
do mpm rundev. But it is already
running. So I don't need to do that. I
can I can see here in the terminal that
it's that it's doing fine. Um close that
terminal. Uh and I'm now going I'm going
to say accept all. And I'm going to
bring back up the camb board. Here it
is. And I'm going to try pressing add
card. Oh. Oh. This is better.
Okay, I like this.
Add card. There it is. It worked. Very
nice. Okay, I think we'll we'll uh we'll
let Gemini off at this point. I think
this is pretty good. I I sort of prefer
to edit it, but but still, I think it's
great. Oh, we haven't checked the delete
works. Let's try that. Yes, delete does
work. All right, I think that is a wrap
for Google Anti-gravity for Gemini. Uh
it seems that uh that it's done a fine
job. I like this a lot. I think it's
very nice. I don't know. What do you
think? For for me, I got to be honest.
For today, I'm giving Codeex the top
position, but it is clearly between uh
Codeex and really I mean GPT 5.2 Codeex
the model running in the Codeex IDE and
that versus Gemini 3 Pro running in
anti-gravity. They both did well. I I
give codeex the win. But it's really
it's your choice. Maybe you've had
completely different answers to me.
Maybe you've got very different results.
You may have used different models. In
which case, please do share them. Share
them in Udemy or email them to me. I'd
love to see them. I would love to see
what you've got. Well, we seem to get
through a lot today, but it was just a
teaser. I wanted to give you the flyby
of cursor, copilot, codeex, and
anti-gravity with the overall takeaway
being that look, they're all quite
similar when the IDE based agents. You
can see that that they often they have a
sidebar on the left or the right that
you can make larger. They often come
with plan mode and and execute mode,
although not all of them. They're mostly
agents.mmd as the way to drive them, but
in the case of anti-gravity, it's the
aagent rules. and and generally you can
see a lot of the same stuff in each of
them and you get very familiar with this
and and really which one you pick
depends on which plan you've paid for or
which one you like or what the rest of
your team are using. Some people are in
for GitHub copilot, some like cursor
which was one of the first that that I
used and uh you know it's really the one
that suits you and your needs the most.
You can do similar things in all of them
and we're going to pick a couple of them
for the next two days for the for the
projects. But really for you, you can
pick whichever one you like. You can do
much the same things and it's more about
now the the focus turns to developing
the right techniques to use these in the
most effective way. And on that note,
tomorrow we will be doing our first
project, the yolo project. I hope you
feel brave as we go into yolo mode. And
uh at this point you should congratulate
yourself cuz somehow already you are 20%
of the way through. You're a fifth of
the way through the program. But don't
worry, that means there's still four
fifths to go.